module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Which of the following online music services launched first?', 
    a: 'Spotify',
    b: 'Apple Music',
    c: 'Tidal',
    d: 'Google Play Music',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many grams are in an ounce?', 
    a: '4',
    b: '8',
    c: '16',
    d: '28',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the offspring of a male donkey and a female horse?', 
    a: 'Tarpan',
    b: 'Mule',
    c: 'Pony',
    d: 'Hinny',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What Chinese game consists of 144 rectangular pieces called tiles?', 
    a: 'Mahjong',
    b: 'Go',
    c: 'Chinese Checkers',
    d: 'Xiangqi',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'In "Alice in Wonderland," what character is always worried about being late?', 
    a: 'The Mad Hatter',
    b: 'White Rabbit',
    c: 'Cheshire Cat',
    d: 'Caterpillar',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the famous mother of CNN anchor, Anderson Cooper?', 
    a: 'Jayne Mansfield',
    b: 'Marilyn Monroe',
    c: 'Gloria Vanderbilt',
    d: 'Sophia Loren',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the opposite of nocturnal?', 
    a: 'Diurnal',
    b: 'Zoonal',
    c: 'Unisonal',
    d: 'Umbonal',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a consumer credit reporting agency?', 
    a: 'TransUnion',
    b: 'Experian',
    c: 'Fannie Mae',
    d: 'Equifax',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the symbol for iron in chemistry?', 
    a: 'Fe',
    b: 'I',
    c: 'Fn',
    d: 'Ir',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which insurance company features an umbrella in its logo?', 
    a: 'Nationwide',
    b: 'State Farm',
    c: 'Travelers',
    d: 'Aflac',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];
